HANA INGRAM

456 Main Street, Albany. NY 09876 h.ingram@myemail.com (876) 543-2109

Knowledgeable and hardworking medical sales representative with an academic background in surgical and laboratory instrument research and development. Proven sales ability with the technical understanding to generate solutions to solve clients' complex clinical problems. Energetic self-starter. Adept at working independently and with colleagues to achieve challenging sales quotas,

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Science In Bioinstru mentation

University At Albany, State University Of New York, Albany, Ny September 2015 - June 2019

KEY SKILLS

- Detailed knowledge of biotech instruments
- Warm and professional communication style
- Secure understanding of effective sales techniques
- · Reliable and hardworking

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MEDICAL SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Gentox Medical Services. Buffalo, NY July 2019 - Present

- Demonstrate skin grafting devices to client clinics and clearly explain their features and benefits
- Manage the sales process from prospecting to close and maintain regular contact with the client before and after the sale to ensure satisfaction
- Actively prospect for new clients using existing professional networks and through medical conferences and events
- Meet with prospective clients to glean insights into their clinical requirements and priorities and suggest cost-effective solutions

TELESALES REPRESENTATIVE

Kleen Windows Incorporated, Buffalo, $\mathbf{N}\mathbf{Y}$

September 2016 - May 2019

- Kept up-to-date and accurate customer records and called potential leads to present the company's service range over the phone
- Described the services available clearly and engagingly and helped customers choose the most appropriate option for their needs
- Remained accountable for meeting personal sales targets, exceeding expectations by 43% in 2018
- Processed orders accurately and efficiently and handled card transactions